bedbathandbeyond.ca 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Bed Bath and Beyond Canada

At Bed Bath & Beyond and Buy Buy Baby, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and therefore do not sell or rent our customers' Personal Information to any third party. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with any third parties for their direct marketing purposes without first providing you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing. You may request information about how we manage your Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy by contacting us at [privacy.information@bedbath.ca](mailto:privacy.information@bedbath.ca) Attn: Privacy Officer.

The www.bedbathandbeyond.ca web site (the " **Site** ") is made available by Bed Bath & Beyond Inc., the parent company to Bed Bath & Beyond Canada L.P., the entity that operates retail store chains in Canada under the names Bed Bath & Beyond and Buy Buy Baby. We refer to Bed Bath & Beyond Inc. and its subsidiaries, including Buy Buy Baby, collectively as "Bed Bath & Beyond", "we", "us" or "our".

This page sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we collect from or are able to obtain about the Site's users. We refer to these policies as our " **Privacy Policy**." In addition to the lower case words "we" "us" and "our" defined above, you will notice that we capitalize certain words in this Privacy Policy even though the rules of grammar do not require that they be capitalized. We do this because these words have specific meanings in this Privacy Policy. These specific meanings are found where the capitalized words are placed in bold text and inside quotation marks.

We hope this Privacy Policy will answer your questions regarding how we treat Personal Information gathered from our Site. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, other than requests related to our managing of your Personal Information, please feel free to contact us at [customer.service@bedbath.ca](mailto:customer.service@bedbath.ca); for more information about your choices regarding your Personal Information, please refer to the section titled "How to Unsubscribe," below. Otherwise please direct all inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy to [privacy.information@bedbath.ca](mailto:privacy.information@bedbath.ca) Attn: Privacy Officer.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to Personal Information that you may provide to us or that we may obtain through means other than the Site, such as by phone or postal mail, but please note that Personal Information obtained through such means will be treated in accordance with the first paragraph above and our use of such Personal Information will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. By accessing and using the Site you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Site. Furthermore, by providing us with Personal Information on this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, use, retention and disclosure of such Personal Information in Canada and/or the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

You may withdraw your consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice to us. If you withdraw your consent, we will inform you of the implications of such withdrawal. To withdraw your consent, simply contact our Privacy Officer at the contact information below and advise us of what Personal Information you no longer wish us to use. All communications with respect to any withdrawal or variation of consent should be in writing and addressed to our Privacy Officer.

As we update and diversify our products and services, this Privacy Policy may change. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page for updates periodically. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here. Unless the law otherwise requires, we do not provide individual notice of changes to this Privacy Policy and your use of the Site following any posted changes will indicate your acceptance of such changes. **This Privacy Policy became effective on December 6, 2007 and was most recently changed on November 28, 2018**. The last change to this policy explained how to find out information about our use of service providers outside Canada.

## What Information Do We Actively Collect and Inactively Gather?

### Personal Information

In order to process orders efficiently, when you place an order with us or register an account on the Site we actively collect the following personal information: name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card information and information that may be of a personally identifiable nature, such as IP addresses, obtained through Tracking Technologies ("Personal Information"). If you prefer not to disclose your Personal Information online, you can always place your order by calling 1-800-GO BEYOND (1-800-462-3966), or visiting one of our stores. Click here to locate the store nearest you and to receive driving directions.

We may periodically conduct surveys of visitors to our Site for internal research purposes that may include marketing. This helps us better understand what our customers would like to see from us. If you respond to such surveys, we may ask you for some Personal Information and/or may contact you for more information, but only if you have given us permission to do so.

We may also receive information about you from other sources.

### Site Usage Information

We (including through our third party service providers) may inactively collect from you information that is not in the same category as Personal Information. For example, we might track information about the date and time you access the Site, the type of web browser you used, and the web site from which you connect to our Site. We collect and use this and other non-Personal Information (such as demographic data) to analyze and develop our business strategy and to determine how you found out about us, your interests regarding our products and services and how to further improve our Site. We, or a third party, may also collect information from your activities on the Site as well as other sites for the purpose of providing advertisements and other content that is customized to your interests and preferences. This means that our ads may appear on participating web sites based upon your browsing activity. To accomplish all this, and also to allow us to offer our customers streamlined ordering and other useful features, we, as do many web sites, use and allow our third party advertising companies to use the technologies listed below and other similar technologies (the " **Tracking Technologies** "):

  * **Cookies and Clear GIFs** \- Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies make web surfing easier for you by saving your customer identification information (i.e., username, password, shopping cart information, etc.) while you're at a site. Cookies also track where you travel on a site and what you look at and purchase. A clear GIF is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page or in an e-mail or other type of message, which is retrieved from a remote site on the Internet enabling the verification of an individual's viewing or receipt of a web page or message.
  * **IP Address Tracking and Clickstream Data** \- In addition to cookies and clear GIFs, our servers automatically collect data about your server's Internet address when you visit our Site. This information, known as an Internet Protocol address, or "IP Address", is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you view pages from our Site, our servers may record or "log" your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server also may record the page that linked you to us and related information including any ads you may have clicked on. Such information is known as " **Clickstream Data** ".
  * **Email Interconnectivity** \- If you receive email from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links or banners it contains and make purchases.

In some cases, we may link the non-Personal information collected through the Tracking Technologies with certain of your Personal Information. WE WANT TO BE SURE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ACCEPTING TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES ONTO YOUR COMPUTER IN NO WAY GIVES US ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. YOU MAY SET YOUR WEB BROWSER SOFTWARE TO REJECT TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES, BUT, IF YOU DO SO, CERTAIN FUNCTIONALITY OF THE SITE MAY BE AFFECTED. Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Site. WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER WHAT INFORMATION SUCH THIRD PARTIES TRACK OR COLLECT, AND HAVE NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY TRACKING, DATA COLLECTION OR OTHER ACTIVITIES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES

### Mobile Devices

You may be visiting the Site from your mobile device. Certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices and we or our third-party service providers may receive such information if you access the Site through mobile devices. Some features of the Site may allow for the collection of mobile phone numbers and we may associate that phone number to mobile device identification information. Furthermore, some mobile phone service providers operate systems that pinpoint the physical location of devices that use their service. Depending on the provider, we or our third-party service providers may receive this information.

You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates may apply when you visit the Site from a mobile device. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device used to visit the Site, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

### Security of the Information You Provide

Among our top priorities is keeping your Personal Information secure. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt all of your Personal Information before it is transmitted to us so that it can be appropriately safeguarded from being read or recorded as it travels over the Internet. You can tell you are sending information securely when you see our Site address change slightly, from http: to https: indicating a secure server connection is being used. The computers that store your Personal Information are located in a separate facility in the United States which employs firewall and security technology. We employ these procedures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

You may be able to create an account on our Site with a username and password, including if you set up a wish list, customer account, or a registry. To help protect your information, we have required password standards. We recommend you exercise extreme care in protecting your password information and do not publicly share any of your passwords. You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of the Site by you or another person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you.

Your Personal Information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding Personal Information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your province or Canada. We use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your Personal Information in a safe, confidential and secure environment in compliance with Canadian privacy legislation. If you object to your Personal Information being transferred or used in this manner please do not register with or use the Site.

ALTHOUGH WE TAKE (AND REQUIRE OUR THIRD-PARTY PROVIDERS TO TAKE) REASONABLE SECURITY PRECAUTIONS TO PROTECT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM AND STORED ON THE SITE, BECAUSE OF THE OPEN NATURE OF THE INTERNET, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED ON OUR SERVERS, TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM A USER, OR OTHERWISE IN OUR CARE WILL BE ABSOLUTELY SAFE FROM INTRUSION BY OTHERS, SUCH AS HACKERS. ACCORDINGLY, WE DISCLAIM ANY LIABILITY FOR ANY THEFT OR LOSS OF, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, OR INTERCEPTION OF ANY DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

### How Do We Use the Information that You Provide and We Collect?

We collect Personal Information for the purposes of fulfilling orders, processing returns and exchanges and providing you with the services you have chosen, providing a high level of customer service, providing you with information we believe may be of interest including mailing our circulars and special offers, for editorial and feedback purposes, for internal marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of your behavior, for product development, for content improvement, for protection against fraud and error, and to customize the content and layout of the Site (collectively, " **Information Usage Purposes** "). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not knowingly use a mobile phone number for marketing purposes without first obtaining your consent. In performing the Information Usage Purposes, we may combine information we collect on the Site with information we receive from other sources. We do not sell Personal Information and we do not disclose Personal Information to any other party, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as required by applicable law or regulatory requirements. Unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, any non-Personal Information you transmit to the Site or we collect from the Site will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and you agree that we may use any such non-Personal Information (together with any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained therein) in any manner, for any purpose, without credit or compensation to you. Without limiting the generality or application of the foregoing, the information that you publish on or through our registries is governed by specific terms available below under the heading "Registry Information".

### Transfer of Your Information; Sharing of Your Information with Our Partners

We may use, store or share Personal Information we collect in the course of our operations in Canada outside of Canada. For example, your Personal Information will be stored and processed on our computers in Canada and the United States. We may also provide your Personal Information to our associates and to third party service providers acting as our authorized agents or partners in providing our services or co-branded services to you and in performing Information Usage Purposes. Our associates and third party service providers may be located outside of Canada. Please refer to the Privacy Officer contact information below to find out information about (i) our practices with respect to the use of service providers outside Canada, and (ii) questions you may have about the collection, use, disclosure or storage of personal information by such service providers located outside Canada.

We use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your Personal Information in a safe, confidential and secure environment in compliance with Canadian privacy legislation. In addition, we screen and reasonably determine to be reputable any such third party to whom we disclose such Personal Information and we require such third parties to agree to use the Personal Information only for such specified purposes and to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your Personal Information in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

If we merge, sell, restructure, or finance or otherwise transfer our assets, Site or operations, or if we are involved in some form of business combination or joint venture, we may disclose or transfer your Personal Information in connection with such transaction provided that, where appropriate, any party to whom the information is disclosed is bound by agreements or obligations, and required to use or disclose your personal information in a manner consistent with the use and disclosure provisions of this Privacy Policy, unless you consent otherwise.

### Registry Information

Wedding and Baby Registry information is treated differently from information submitted for other purposes on our Site. Registry users may receive additional e-mail communications from us, such as a registry welcome e-mail and follow-up contact after the scheduled event date or the baby's expected arrival date. In addition, cookies are used as part of our registry service to save your registry number on your computer. By registering with us and opting to make your registry available online, your registry information, which includes your name, the province where you live, your event, event date or baby's expected arrival date, and type of event will be available publicly and may be used by our partners that help provide our services and our co-branded services (including for Information Usage Purposes) and will be accessible by search engines and spiders that are not affiliated with us.

Finally, and to illustrate the type of business partner with whom your registry information may be shared, if you have taken advantage of the applicable opt-in procedure, your registry information (your name, province where you live, date of event, baby's expected arrival date and event location) may be made available to third party wedding and baby registry portal sites. We may also share the e-mail address associated with your registry, but solely to enable us and such a third-party registry portal site to link your purchases or other activity with the registry you have established with us. The use of such portal sites is intended to provide your guests with additional means of finding your registry, and to provide you with additional ways to create a registry with us. Any third-party registry portal site with whom an e-mail address is shared as a registry identifier is contractually prohibited from using it for any other purpose not outlined above. In the future, if you wish to unsubscribe from our sharing of your information with such sites, please send an e-mail to [customer.service@bedbath.ca](mailto:customer.service@bedbath.ca) clearly indicating such request.

### Use of Information in Sweepstakes and Contests

Occasionally, we may run a promotion such as a sweepstakes or a contest (a "Promotion"), and you will be given the opportunity to enter by filling out an entry form, or in some cases, you may be automatically entered by using a designated type of credit card when placing an order in store, online or via phone or, for example, by creating a Wedding or Baby Registry. Your entry information may be shared with third parties for the limited purposes of administering the sweepstakes and selecting a winner(s) and may be used to notify you in connection with the sweepstakes or contest and to verify your identity. When you enter such a Promotion, you will have the opportunity to consent to receive future communications from us. Since we value your privacy, you will always have the opportunity to stop such communications as detailed below. In addition, some Promotions may have one or more co-sponsors, and you may also be asked upon entry to consent to receive future communications from such co-sponsors. In the event your consent is indicated, the information from your entry will be shared with the co-sponsors. In those situations, the third parties will have the right to use your information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies, and we are not responsible for how co-sponsors may use your information. In all events, we will make it clear to you in the entry, order or registration form, before you submit it, whether you are consenting to receive information from any party, and you will be given the opportunity to confirm or withdraw such consent prior to submitting your entry, order or registration.

In any case, where you elect to have us share your information with third parties, such as in the Promotions discussed above, those elections to have your information shared will supersede anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy.

### How to Unsubscribe

We will only send e-mail for customer service purposes and to those visitors who have indicated that they wish to receive other types of e-mail from us and our subsidiaries.

If at any time you wish to stop receiving e-mail from us, we include an unsubscribe mechanism in all of our e-mails and you can always remove your name from our mailing list by sending an e-mail to [customer.service@bedbath.ca](mailto:customer.service@bedbath.ca) stating that you wish to unsubscribe and indicating in the subject line of the e-mail "NO E-MAIL". Although we will promptly remove your name from our e-mail list upon receiving your request, it is possible that you may still receive e-mails from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed from our list.

THE UNSUBSCRIBE RIGHTS AND PROCEDURES DESCRIBED IN THIS SECTION ARE THE DEFAULT RULES AND PROCEDURES WE USE IN OPERATING THE SITE AND ARE THE STANDARD BY WHICH WE ADHERE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.

Please keep in mind that, if you choose not to receive marketing communications, you will continue to receive transactional or account communications related to services or products that you have requested on the Site (e.g. confirmation e-mails, billing reminders).

### Release of Information to Protect Our Site and Others

We may release Personal Information as permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements, to comply with valid legal processes such as search warrants, subpoenas or court orders, to seek advice from our legal counsel, as part of our regular reporting activity to related companies, to protect the rights, property or safety of Bed Bath & Beyond, Buy Buy BABY, our users or others, to address emergency situations or where necessary to protect the safety of a person or group, to enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or where the Personal Information is publicly available.

### Your Account Access Rights

You may review and make changes to the Personal Information that is stored in your user account on the Site by visiting the "My Account" area of the Site.

You can request access to your Personal Information stored by Bed Bath & Beyond by contacting our Privacy Officer (contact information below) and we will inform you about what type of Personal Information we have on record or in our control, how it is used and to whom it may have been disclosed, provide you with access to your information so you can review and verify the accuracy and completeness and request changes to the information and make any necessary updates to your Personal Information.

There are instances where applicable law or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide some or all of the Personal Information that we hold about you. In addition, the Personal Information may have been destroyed, erased or made anonymous in accordance with our record retention obligations and practices. If we do not provide you with access to your Personal Information, we will endeavor to inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions.

### Intended Users; Use by Children under 13

The Site is not purposefully directed at children under the age of 13 and all products available for sale on the Site are intended to be purchased by adults. We do not collect or maintain Personal Information, via the Site or otherwise, from those we actually know are children under 13 years of age. If you notify us that information has been provided by a child under the age of 13, upon verification, we will promptly delete such information.

### Third Party Ad Servers; Links to Other Web Sites

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. The Site also may contain links to other web sites that are not under our control. These links may include the use of so-called "share links." A "share link" is a button and/or text link appearing on our Site that enables the launch of a sharing mechanism whereby you can post links to, and content from, the Site onto social networking web sites such as Facebook. The privacy policies of other web site operators or advertisers may significantly differ from our Privacy Policy. We urge you to read the privacy statements of each and every web site you visit and to contact the third-party Web site operators or advertisers directly if you have any questions or concerns about their data collection or privacy policies. For example, to enhance your experience on this Site, we use Google Maps APIs including at account and registry creation, and at checkout. Google has specifically requested that we inform you that your use of such services is subject to the [Google Maps/Google Earth Additional Terms of Service](https://maps.google.com/help/terms_maps.html) (including the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us)). WE HAVE NO CONTROL OR INFLUENCE OVER THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF SUCH OTHER WEB SITES AND ADVERTISERS AND WE DO NOT ASSUME ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD-PARTY WEB SITE OPERATORS' OR ADVERTISERS' DATA COLLECTION PRACTICES, THEIR FAILURE TO ABIDE BY THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES OR THE CONTENT OF ANY THIRD PARTY WEB SITES.

### Inquiries or Concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about how we manage your Personal Information, including how your Personal Information is collected, stored or processed by third party service providers outside of Canada, please contact our Privacy Officer. If you are dissatisfied with our response, you may be entitled to make a written submission to the federal Privacy Commissioner.

### Privacy Officer

We have appointed a Privacy Officer to oversee compliance with this Privacy Policy. The contact information for our Privacy Officer is as follows:

  * Privacy Officer
  * Bed Bath & Beyond Canada L.P.,
  * 845 Marine Drive
  * Unit 200 North Vancouver B.C. Canada, V7P 1R7
  * T. 1-877-222-5939
  * E. [ privacy.information@bedbath.ca](mailto:privacy.information@bedbath.ca)

### Interpretation of this Privacy Policy

Any interpretation associated with this Privacy Policy will be made by our Privacy Officer. This Privacy Policy does not create or confer upon any individual any rights, or impose upon Bed Bath & Beyond any rights or obligations in addition to any rights or obligations imposed by Canada's applicable federal and provincial privacy laws. Should there be any inconsistency between this Privacy Policy and the applicable federal and provincial privacy laws, this Privacy Policy will be interpreted so as to give effect to, and comply with, those privacy laws which are applicable.
